<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<recording_script>
  <fileid id="z0001_000">Other Navy award: Navy Cross.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_001">Toes drag while walking</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_002">John Williams as Lee Williams</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_003">This also gives a term</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_004">This national movement, which had begun with so much hope, came to a sad end.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_005">Japanese Cinema Database (Agency for Cultural Affairs).</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_006">But there are some bright spots.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_007">Joseph High School, every week of the school year.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_008">He also added a summer school program.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_009">After a one-year break Zero Degree was her following venture.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_010">M T V At The Movies</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_011">She left the Catholic church when she moved away from home to attend college.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_012">Mercy B. Jackson, M.D.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_013">I guess that will hold them for a while.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_014">With help of the points</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_015">To eight thirty p.m.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_016">Since he was ten, Howard has supported Liverpool Football Club.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_017">The team has never won a game yet.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_018">Foot drops: unable to hold the foot straight across</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_019">Ordered by position on pitch (from back right to front left).</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_020">They were granted access back into the house after five days.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_021">Robert E. Miller as Coach Wilson</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_022">A new parish hall (without a barn) has only in recent years been built.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_023">nineteen ninety four James Last</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_024">by placing small art objects throughout the film.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_025">The album later broke the Diamond record on Q Q Music.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_026">She was more wrapped up in doing the work.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_027">But my conviction is that I have suffered for things that I am guilty of.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_028">What a sensation that would cause.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_029">Do they rise to the occasion and challenges or do they fail?</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_030">One of the deaths took place after twenty or more days in hospital with severe head-wounds.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_031">The Impact of Rising Food Prices on the Poor.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_032">This theme is in all of my books.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_033">eighty eight and a third single "Keep the Fire Burning" failed to chart.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_034">buying a new car, making a mean comment.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_035">The home city for both acts is the Black Family Estate.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_036">He had a partner, with whom he had two children.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_037">To this end, a new double-track bridge was proposed.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_038">Promoted as "Big Brother goes evil", Big Brother five saw numerous changes occurring to the game.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_039">The Rays sought feedback from their players on who should manage the team.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_040">It stayed all common law suits against the Earl.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_041">The cost is one dollar per issue or thirty dollars per year.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_042">Its headquarters are in Sheffield, United Kingdom.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_043">It is found in North America.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_044">The church is dedicated to saint George.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_045">He was also involved in hunting and fishing.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_046">Loss of profit on intended sales.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_047">After getting the right measurements they made the new doors.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_048">Committee on Education and the Workforce</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_049">It is found in South Africa.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_050">There was a nine rank system, each rank having more power than the lower rank.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_051">In an interview with the B B C he said.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_052">Simon Read two thousand and twelve</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_053">He also allowed only eighty three hits.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_054">It does not use radiation.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_055">In the early stages came close to us asleep.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_056">On tenth February, he scored the only goal in a victory over Liverpool.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_057">Early on, the company was recognized for technical leadership but was largely unable to turn leadership into revenues and profits.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_058">He lives like he is a young person.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_059">He was a member of the Yes Scotland Advisory Board.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_060">Pope Gregory the third made a large payment to the duke to restore the castle to him.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_061">It flowers between July and September.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_062">Upon release, the film received positive reviews and was a huge box office success.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_063">In the summer weekends, getting car space on the ferry usually requires advance booking.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_064">Adult, vocational and higher education programs are also available.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_065">The post office was named for R.C.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_066">As a result of all the arguments getting to her.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_067">A Journal of Global Cultural Studies.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_068">A tour followed in support.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_069">Along with the covers, it includes a new, original recording: Good.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_070">The man said he would stay with his bear anyway.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_071">So with ten players, the lift continued to push for the second goal, but without much success.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_072">Both teams were trying to impose their rhythm, more than two wings.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_073">Unlike the Catholic who would tend to focus on the external factor.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_074">It opened on October twentieth, eighteen eighty</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_075">The Director had to carry out his statutory functions with a view to the reduction of crime.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_076">Doctor of Philosophy in Engineering Management</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_077">describes appointments of an acting Chief Justice or Judge of the Supreme Court.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_078">He still believed the first half of Matthew represented the Western text-type.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_079">The S S A aimed to build a left-wing alternative to New Labour and the S N P.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_080">The rest of the shares were offered to public market.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_081">They take those films on a small run and allow them to see the light of day.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_082">The ISS itself generally can last about forty five minutes in this mode.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_083">This took away the main argument of safety risks.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_084">Jackson cared for these children as her own.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_085">By word of mouth, Jackson became known to many women across the country.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_086">The building was designed, built and financed by the Chinese government.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_087">Many argue that the seemingly crude language used to describe women throughout the novel is anti-feminist.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_088">Among the four press conferences, three of them were public speeches without questions and answers.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_089">He was featured as one of the guests in House of Mouse.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_090">The camp was established in eighteen forty eight during the California Gold Rush.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_091">His gesture earned him the winning bid, although there was very little competition.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_092">Right Here Right Now, his two thousand and eleven arena tour, sold out.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_093">It specifically rewards horror on television.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_094">The new support error resolution steps are recorded in the knowledge base for future use.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_095">He earned his P H D.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_096">It went on to sell three hundred thousand units, achieve five No.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_097">It was produced by Michael Sweet.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_098">They often had a monopoly, and were suspected of sharp practice.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_099">Theatre activities are still popular today in the kingdom.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_100">Tom was one of ten children.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_101">A governing National Executive Committee of five members was elected.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_102">The club later lost in the quarter-finals to Russian club C S K A Moscow.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_103">the destruction of Arab residential compounds</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_104">It was a battle in the long-running series of Gothic Wars.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_105">Big Brother five was the third of the main series to feature a live launch.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_106">He was charged with planning to set off bombs in Europe and the United States.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_107">Church of All Saints also called Church of Saint Michael</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_108">For such cases, only the horizontal (east and north) components matter.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_109">Six teams have been divided in two groups of three teams each.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_110">His wife is Jean, and their daughter is Isabel.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_111">He was a fellow of the Royal Society of Literature.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_112">He died on sixth September fifteen fifty three</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_113">Its growth was greatly influenced by the cloth factory founded in eighteen thirty</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_114">Listening into her chest, he can hear the sound of the river within her.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_115">It contains a lot of pictures.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_116">His mother died a year later.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_117">In two thousand and three, US News said that it got them.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_118">Let them go to the Supreme Court now and see what they can get out of them.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_119">He also appeared in Belgium, Switzerland, Canada, and North Africa.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_120">He is amazed by her existence, as he considers her neither woman nor bird.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_121">We demand tax reforms to ensure that corporations and the wealthy pay their fair share in taxes.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_122">So many others left China with the same dream but ended up with their dreams shattered.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_123">The building is scheduled to open to the public in two thousand and twenty</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_124">He signed on for a year, but left the job after just four months.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_125">It took three years to complete the project.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_126">He holds that "every life is a precious gift from God that begins from the moment of conception."</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_127">"Packed in Its Own Juice" was on the bottom of the stamp.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_128">Derby Miller is on "Troubles They Are But Few"</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_129">The Voice of the People Volume fourteen</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_130">He joined the Royal Air Force during the Second World War.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_131">They were established in eighteen seventy one and are one of the oldest clubs in the South of England.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_132">In two thousand and ten, Google Voice became available without invitation.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_133">Zero to zero to seal the efforts of the players of both teams.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_134">The AEL has tried to impose its rhythm on the lift to wait and grow gradually.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_135">Approved seventeenth April nineteen forty five</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_136">She also took part in the two thousand and four "Walk in the Clouds" show and fashion collection.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_137">The budget for the new bridge project was established at five point six million dollars  Canadian.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_138">However the town she lives in, no one wants to hear about her.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_139">It flows to the east.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_140">Our film had a strong reception in Europe and achieved distribution, but that was not the case here.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_141">The desire for more stories about the "tragic hero" became requested.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_142">The first show was held on August second, two thousand and three</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_143">His regular playing position was on the wing.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_144">The film was a commercial success.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_145">The hospital is scheduled to fully open in two thousand and nine</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_146">She described the story as a "precious work" that had help her build social connections.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_147">Both the port and the factory were destroyed in World War two</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_148">The wings were now made in a single pressing.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_149">However, it is tape-delayed and broadcast after the Derby.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_150">But returning for two matches in a week in August, he scored just nine against Hampshire.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_151">On joining the club, Mills was given the number five shirt ahead of the new season.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_152">You are a great people.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_153">He writes about film for Film Ireland Magazine.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_154">He lost via split decision and was subsequently released from the promotion.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_155">She reached the grand-finals in which she came third overall.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_156">And I always said to the employees of American, 'This is not an appropriate investment.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_157">He has also contributed to the New York Review of Books.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_158">and a Ph.D.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_159">This request number is used to track the progress on the support issue.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_160">The second monitor also displays the time left for playing.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_161">It succeeded the Y Board and System twenty four, combining features from both.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_162">I asked how much it would cost to buy just the chip and they came back with two million dollars.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_163">The Independent does not receive funding from the U S G or the G S O.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_164">twenty three on the Top forty charts.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_165">One of which was the Gulf War inspired "Believe".</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_166">They wait for a time, building up their forces, beginning to wonder if this evil really exists.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_167">two thousand: Even So Come</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_168">The time between these points is variable and can occur anywhere from a minute to much longer.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_169">Today the line is designated by the Polish State Railways (P K P) as Rail Line two</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_170">Physical therapy exercises may help patients to maintain muscle strength.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_171">Their non-conference opponents were from the NFC West.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_172">From the first minutes both teams showed their desire to compete with aggressive approaches.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_173">Whether the air flow is free or forced can affect the energy efficiency of the window.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_174">In the laboratory, bacteria are usually grown using solid or liquid media.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_175">Therefore, there is a need to closely monitor these patients for much longer than usual.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_176">It is found in Mexico.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_177">Master of Science in Engineering Management</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_178">Judges of the Supreme Court shall hold office until the age of retirement of sixty-five years.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_179">It was issued in five volumes for the New Testament. One to four volumes for the Old Testament</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_180">The Scottish Government of two thousand and seven to eleven later picked up the bill and introduced it themselves.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_181">The changes observed represent the mass flow rate and density of the fluid.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_182">It is found in Africa, Europe and Northern Asia (excluding China), North America, and Southern Asia.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_183">He calls the top Conference Final and the entire Stanley Cup Finals for both networks.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_184">It was first broadcast on third January two thousand and ten</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_185">The continued use of using public writing as a platform for telling the Indian story was questioned.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_186">For every one hundred females, there are eighty five point zero males.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_187">one thousand eight hundred and forty six, fourth edition.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_188">was replaced with the full development of G P S.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_189">They come up with a very cruel way of ending the relationship.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_190">Joseph High School and the schools they compete against in all sports.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_191">It became an official journal of I S C B in two thousand and five</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_192">Actually, I had never been to a village before that.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_193">Jonathan Richardson was an Irish politician.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_194">The electron transport chain is not affected and continues using oxygen, without producing A T P.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_195">The front-wheel drive range was reduced to three models, L X, G T, and I E.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_196">Two All-Star Games were held each season from nineteen fifty nine to nineteen sixty two</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_197">The National League dominated from nineteen fifty to nineteen eighty seven, winning thirty three of forty two with one tie.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_198">Since nineteen ninety nine, the All-Star Futures Game has been held during All-Star Week.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_199">In two thousand and six, he signed with Manchester City.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_200">Very shortly after, Jackson met her second husband, captain Daniel Jackson who had four children from a previous marriage.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_201">Nothing could be more false.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_202">The average household size was two point two seven and the average family size was three point zero zero</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_203">Russia is recognized for its nuclear disaster expertise and for the safety of its technology.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_204">More flexible is the second paper strip method.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_205">Statistics show that sexual violence and domestic violence are increasing in these years.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_206">Work on the E E S started in March two thousand and seven at a cost of five million dollars million.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_207">In other ways, however, the college had its trials and changes.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_208">Accordingly, four P E V bishops have been appointed across the two provinces.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_209">In two thousand and eleven, the team scored two goals, the highest scoring at a tournament so far.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_210">We are justified by Christ alone and not by our believing, Richardson claimed.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_211">It was recorded at That Studio in North Hollywood.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_212">The I U C N Red List of Threatened Species.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_213">Volume two, numbers one, two, and three</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_214">nineteen seventy two: Hits of the Decade</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_215">nineteen seventy eight: His Love Put a Song in My Heart</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_216">We listened to all of them and decided to wait until the next day to choose one.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_217">All we can do is to try and make M A F F see sense.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_218">Both of the versions feature the song "Happy Holiday".</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_219">None of the passengers or crew were injured.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_220">The image of the game said that the team that scores first will win</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_221">Using the most used start formation.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_222">twelve plus one match ban per card</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_223">They all offer different units, supports, and improvements.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_224">His first review was of a concert by Jan and Dean.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_225">one Sales and Use Tax.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_226">She is intelligent and sympathetic.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_227">For every one hundred females age eighteen and over, there were eighty four point two males.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_228">eleven ninety five to twelve oh three</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_229">He died on eighteenth April nineteen sixty</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_230">The first B M W M five was produced during the E twenty eight generation.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_231">two thousand and five Gentleman</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_232">two thousand and three Can</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_233">In two thousand and twelve the criteria for entry included album release date and "two outstanding reviews from music journalists."</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_234">For every one hundred females age eighteen and over, there are eighty five point seven males.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_235">He was promoted to the major league team on September first, two thousand and fourteen</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_236">He was re-elected in nineteen fifteen and nineteen eighteen, serving through nineteen twenty one</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_237">In New York City in nineteen oh six on F.O.E.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_238">This led him to attend school properly only at the age of nine and a half</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_239">Its name means "central" in Korean.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_240">Several small rivers flow through the town.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_241">His first sports job was a production position at ESPN in nineteen ninety two</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_242">In the ninth century he was an Irish poet.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_243">As of two thousand and fourteen, MTV is available within the United Kingdom on Virgin Media and Sky.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_244">This has also included situations where the person is no longer actively managing a team.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_245">The album was released in Australia on nineteenth August two thousand and eleven</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_246">Adults are active in the summer and in the spring.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_247">Members are required to comply with the code of professional conduct and practice it</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_248">Sometimes their position gives them power by placing them at the top of a political hierarchy.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_249">Mills finished the season having made forty-two appearances and scoring five times in the league.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_250">Over the course of their time together, Mercy and Daniel had eight children together, only four of whom survived.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_251">During the trial, he said that his lawyers had opposed putting him on the stand.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_252">In these circumstances a verdict of not guilty would have been very unusual.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_253">Brief mention of the conviction appeared on page three of the New York Times.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_254">Shakespeare: many references are made to scenes, interactions, or characters from various plays.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_255">Letters sent from Lieutenant-Governors may also bear the O.H.M.S.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_256">This is often described as a body mass index (BMI) over thirty</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_257">Method one the first method</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_258">Thus, Park considers the American-South Korean alliance as the most successful one in the world.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_259">The church closed in two thousand and fourteen</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_260">The college had never more than eight students at a time, and had often so few as five.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_261">He had to leave the college after four years.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_262">nineteen ninety nine: P.I.G.S.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_263">In Australian waters, this ray has been assessed as of Least Concern.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_264">"I still go down the pub and play football with my mates", he commented in two thousand and ten</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_265">An Introduction to Greek Tragedy.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_266">The club was founded in nineteen seventy four</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_267">The official single of that debut album, "Paris Calling" had an elaborate music video.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_268">Some of them have storage functions for security and back-up of valuable business information.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_269">If it is a new support error, then new issue resolution steps are created and the error is resolved.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_270">She was born on-screen during the episode broadcast on fourth November nineteen ninety four</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_271">They talk to Sally but she tells them they are too young and they do not have her permission.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_272">The club folded in two thousand and twelve</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_273">one road layer, can draw two roads at once</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_274">Popular songs of this period include "Get Away Jordan" and "Happy Rhythm".</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_275">He then moved to Washington D.C. and was a partner with Ward Brown until nineteen twenty nine</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_276">The plea and threatened legal challenge was ultimately successful.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_277">He died in Canada in two thousand and four</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_278">In addition, US joint venture facilities were also been similarly extended.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_279">A section of this track was removed, and the parking lot built in its place.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_280">Physical therapy can help patients to learn how to walk with a foot drop.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_281">Treat injuries to the leg or knee right away.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_282">Three maximum breaks have been made in the history of the tournament, all by overseas players.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_283">India had a disappointing tournament and never looked likely to progress beyond the round robin.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_284">The State Council went through important personnel and structural changes following the seventeenth Party Congress.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_285">He played with ten players for half, was against the tradition in GSP.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_286">He stayed at twenty seven degrees the "Lady" and risk losing valuable ground in the race for first place.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_287">A team can use only five foreign players on the field in each game.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_288">James lived there until his death in nineteen twenty when he was ninety five years of age.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_289">He came with his family to Australia at the age of ten in eighteen thirty five</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_290">The couple had five children, three sons and two daughters.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_291">Three days later, he assisted on a goal in a two to zero League Cup win over Newcastle United.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_292">The club became registered in two thousand and eleven and played its first season in two thousand and twelve</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_293">What also lost again, a chance for a regional title.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_294">The test was easy, however, for negative events.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_295">He remained world champion until nineteen sixty five, a year in which he suffered a terrible accident.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_296">A small business owner, Broad operated his wheat and sheep farm for sixteen years from the age of twenty two</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_297">Every users are provided Identity Card with Bar-code Technology.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_298">The jury awarded the shareholders two hundred and eighty million dollars million in damages.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_299">one security officer was killed as well, and another wounded.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_300">Its main offices were in London, with a second office Belfast.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_301">In Scotland, civil recovery was achieved through the Civil Recovery Unit of the Scottish Government.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_302">Data reported by researchers in October two thousand and twelve was published in March two thousand and thirteen</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_303">The family drives a nineteen fifty seven Ford Custom three hundred in the first two seasons.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_304">A third series of Death in Paradise was commissioned for early two thousand and fourteen</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_305">Miller explained he had personal reasons for the change.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_306">The series ended on sixth August two thousand and four, lasting for a total of seventy one days.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_307">Ferguson faced no general election opponent in the heavily Democratic district.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_308">He declined to take a pay raise during tough economic times.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_309">During the course of the campaign, Ferguson visited all thirty nine Washington state counties.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_310">A letter by Ferguson called for a penalty of two thousand dollars Dollars and to celebrate all same sex unions.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_311">The nineteen ninety nine judgment noted that "the influence of the father of the accused has been there".</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_312">The video for Blood War was released in June two thousand and ten</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_313">They established diplomatic relations on September nineteenth, nineteen seventy two</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_314">He is currently serving a fifteen year prison term arising from those charges.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_315">This means that the plaintiff must prove each element of the claim, or cause of action in order to recover.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_316">Here, he was heavily involved in the leadership of the anti-poll tax struggle which brought down Margaret Thatcher.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_317">The main customers came from Imperial Russia and the most significant one was the Imperial Russian Navy.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_318">The product was well received, and its company was a success.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_319">Very few people ever get clean on the first or second attempt.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_320">The method assumes a database of commonly accepted knowledge that, along with other commitments, provides premises for arguments.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_321">The village structure shown in his map is to a great extent unchanged today.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_322">One of the groups is there to protect the universe, the other is there to destroy it.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_323">Awards are decided by a twelve-member jury based on critical and commercial appeal.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_324">In August nineteen ninety three, one hundred and fifty thousand copies had been sold on the Spanish market.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_325">Candidate sites must also submit a work plan.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_326">The draw for the Qualifying Round was held on sixteenth February two thousand and eight in Venice, Italy.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_327">There were four groups, one group of five teams and three groups of four teams.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_328">The English translation by Steven T. Murray was published in nineteen ninety seven</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_329">Three years later he was promoted to the rank of lieutenant colonel and to full colonel in nineteen oh eight</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_330">if only the program could break out, just a little, from its too-familiar approach.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_331">There were four hundred and eighteen households.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_332">The New York Times published his discovery shortly before Christmas in nineteen sixty six</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_333">After nineteen forty nine, he worked for the Publicity Department of the Communist Party of China.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_334">He is also active in worldwide efforts for achieving gender balance in the physical sciences.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_335">The bank is jointly owned by him and his brothers and relatives.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_336">He committed suicide in two thousand and seventeen after the sudden death of his partner.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_337">In nineteen sixty seven congress granted approval for the construction of Tunnel nine</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_338">As of two thousand and seventeen, the student council represents more than one thousand students worldwide.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_339">Her literature was well received in both Portugal and Brazil.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_340">He later attended public schools when they opened in his area, and learned Latin.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_341">He also represented the Republican Party at several conventions.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_342">He elected free agency on November sixth, two thousand and seventeen</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_343">The results were published on twenty third June two thousand and sixteen</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_344">The bill went into full effect on first July two thousand and fifteen</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_345">The Dutch Government is currently examining the legal consequences of the ruling.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_346">The film has been met with positive reviews by critics.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_347">There were only fifty RHD factory built cars, none of which were officially imported to the UK.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_348">The channel was set up to provide audiences with local artists and more relevant music content.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_349">Club MTV is the channel plays dance, EDM and urban music, replacing MTV Dance.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_350">Local programming includes MTV News and The Festival Show.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_351">The channel was replaced with Club MTV on twenty third May two thousand and eighteen</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_352">The channel shown content from sister channels MTV and Comedy Central.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_353">At this point, it is ensured that every team is represented by at least one player.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_354">From nineteen thirty three to nineteen forty nine, the American League won twelve out of the first sixteen</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_355">A part of Little England beyond Wales, it has been essentially English-speaking for nine hundred years.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_356">He switched to rival Nottingham Forest in two thousand and fifteen</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_357">These teams were classified into three performing categories: high, medium and low.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_358">The prosecution also brought out that both men had fled the draft by going to Mexico in nineteen seventeen</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_359">In October nineteen twenty seven, H. G. Wells wrote an essay that discussed the case at length.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_360">However, the village remained isolated until the arrival of the first newspaper, Second Republic.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_361">In use since the eighteenth century, it is today still used but is a somewhat dated term.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_362">The book has inspired both an opera, and a museum exhibition.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_363">The proof follows from a straightforward calculation.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_364">The miners repeatedly fought them off with their tools.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_365">Its original owners claimed in court they were forced to turn it over to her father.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_366">Park has been criticized for picking the wrong people for senior government posts.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_367">Even in the remaining press conference, the questions were submitted in advance and she read prepared answers.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_368">It was opened on eighteenth January two thousand and thirteen</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_369">The three-story brick building was constructed in eighteen ninety three</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_370">The home was built and lived in by Andrew Jackson Kennedy, deputy collector for the Internal Revenue Service.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_371">Some of the countries have surveys for multiple years.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_372">The only exception is the Green Line which operates Monday through Friday only from six a.m.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_373">In two thousand and sixteen, the group gave him a zero percent rating.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_374">In Australia, it is one of several species referred to as "bull ray".</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_375">Due to overwhelming demand he further extended the tour twice into two thousand and nine</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_376">This was further extended to include more UK dates in December two thousand and fourteen</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_377">He completed the twenty six mile course in four hours and fifteen minutes, beating his target time of five hours.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_378">He played twelve games for the club and scored forty nine points, including three field goals.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_379">The ministry had twenty Cabinet ministers including the Chief Minister and nine Ministers of State.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_380">Business applications can fail when an unexpected error occurs.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_381">The request is assigned to a support team member.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_382">This information is then recorded in the support request.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_383">The application program is reviewed for any possible programming errors.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_384">The first wedding between a same-sex couple at Saint George.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_385">The first service in the new church was held in nineteen fifty one, although the building was not fully finished.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_386">The club had three senior sides playing in the Liverpool and District Cricket Competition.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_387">It was also used by several other companies from nineteen eighty four to nineteen eighty seven</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_388">He subsequently went to school in Bristol.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_389">The concert has increasingly become a scene of drug use and violence over the years.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_390">Admission to the museum is free.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_391">They follow policy guidelines and gain increasing ranks within the system.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_392">It rose up and drove them all out of the house.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_393">There are only seventeen days over thirty degrees, and seventy over twenty five degrees.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_394">RAF Fighter Command Victory Claims, Part Two.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_395">The Longest Tunnel: The True Story of World War II's Great Escape.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_396">It is found in Australia, where it has been recorded from New South Wales.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_397">The group currently has a presence in eighty countries and is one of the largest business groups in northern Spain.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_398">Undertaking was offered a chance to submit a song for this LP.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_399">Like the uniform, the school sports colours are black and white.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_400">The village is famous for its artistic character.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_401">With the later he made friends and their friendship lasted for many years.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_402">A Liberal-Conservative, he was defeated in eighteen eighty two</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_403">We were willing to take this topic on when others were not, and people appreciate that.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_404">We needed to spend more time letting our friends know where this was going.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_405">In early two thousand and thirteen, a paid version XE Currency Pro was made available for iPhone users.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_406">He is member of the Court of the Royal College of Art, London, UK.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_407">He was also a three time French national champion nineteen ninety, nineteen ninety four, two thousand and one</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_408">The inclusion of wild-card players meant that there were an additional two or three matches to be arranged.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_409">Education reforms which include free nine years of education and education initiatives to assist with the rural regions.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_410">Instead, there are a number of new concepts introduced, whilst existing concepts have been expanded.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_411">The rights and duties of persons (natural persons and legal persons) amongst themselves is the primary concern of civil law.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_412">In the process of its construction modern materials and techniques were used such as reinforced concrete and expanded metal.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_413">Construction was completed by December nineteen sixty one, and the system came into operation in early nineteen sixty two</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_414">After playing a sell-out show in Glasgow, Scotland, members of the band and crew were involved in heavy drinking.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_415">Some were put on general sale, while others were reserved to specific markets, owners clubs or selected customers.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_416">Lay also officially signed the contract on stage with the director and producers of The Golden Eyes.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_417">The French Revolution and the Industrial Revolution changed the dress code for men and women not only in France.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_418">But sadly, after nineteen years of marriage, her second husband died of cancer in eighteen fifty two</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_419">There are now over one hundred stores in operation in the world (currently in Australia, New Zealand, the United Kingdom).</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_420">Some publications and fan-voted lists have considered it to be one of the best games of all time.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_421">Someone did break, however, and the case is strong that it was Number Two who fell to pieces.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_422">It was released in the United States on July twenty third, nineteen ninety nine</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_423">They are marked by strong.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_424">The Visigoths, in turn, were succeeded by the Moors.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_425">Lazy to get the game</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_426">The next day, we talked.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_427">He plays at Fly-half.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_428">At Slate, Willa Paskin was more enthused.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_429">Marsha Jones is CJ's mother.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_430">Yet he also shared his own doubts.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_431">Church community groups meet here.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_432">No other newspapers followed suit.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_433">There he fell sick with typhus himself.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_434">I think I might be nothing.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_435">Ermite is a blue cheese.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_436">The couple had no issue.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_437">a strip of paper of length</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_438">"Theme Song from 'Which Way Is Up'" was a hit song by RB female vocal group Stargard.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_439">June is a full-time homemaker.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_440">On Day nine, Housemates were given their new task.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_441">However, this proved short-lived.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_442">For the proof one shows that point</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_443">Mark Hopkins, junior railroad financier</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_444">But there are those who see her very differently.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_445">Joseph plays, are featured each week on the show.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_446">She appeared in his debut film Decoy.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_447">Over time, the doctor observes that his wife does not age.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_448">two thousand five: Hip-Hop Honeys: Las Vegas</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_449">The dragon body was drawn in a boat shape.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_450">She fears they will get a divorce but this never happens.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_451">"Thou art a fool," the old man said.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_452">David Wojnarowicz: Brush Fires in the Social Landscape.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_453">Clair, Michigan with his wife Joyce.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_454">The phone call changes his life.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_455">Kentview is a suburb of Johannesburg, South Africa.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_456">Most of the user interface as well as all Java FX eye-candies was removed.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_457">Macduff swears revenge and joins forces with Malcolm to overthrow Macbeth.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_458">Keep your hands to yourself.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_459">However, they are ambushed by a group of Mohawks and head to a village nearby.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_460">It is not known how much, if any, of her claims are true.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_461">I don't know what I am.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_462">For any method described below</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_463">The authors claimed that high-power poses "produce power".</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_464">Tom Wolf for the homophobic comment.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_465">The law is therefore valid.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_466">The value of lost lobsters.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_467">The name stuck after that.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_468">There is also a midline row of sharp tubercles on the back, with two shorter rows alongside.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_469">Reviewed in Cyprus Review volume three.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_470">I liked playing the role.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_471">Alder, who was born in Glasgow, was a foster child.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_472">The special was titled Dope Luxurious Cribs.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_473">I thought it was ruined.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_474">The entire world is safe again, though horribly shaken.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_475">The song is called "Blood War".</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_476">The upper tier of the tower has a semicircular window openings.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_477">Fewer and fewer flights are on time.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_478">He helps gather the Sioux and Cheyenne nations and fights with them at the Little Bighorn.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_479">The Reaper is coming for you" as a threat to "Mad Dog" Adair and his ally John White.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_480">Kay McShane is a former Irish wheelchair athlete.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_481">The wearing of skirts by men is also found in the goth subculture.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_482">The proof for the pair</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_483">His voice is described as "squeaky".</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_484">New York: Penguin Random House.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_485">Thus the cull was not carried out.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_486">Its motto is "whoever you are and wherever you are on the journey of faith, you are welcome here".</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_487">He then traveled throughout Europe.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_488">Casts on lower leg due to tightness</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_489">He appears in school plays as a mushroom and a Dutch boy.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_490">However, she still gives birth prematurely.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_491">It also gathered data on cloud thickness and light intensity in the atmosphere.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_492">Each group played a knockout tournament.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_493">This version is noted for being very faithful to the original novel.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_494">County residents approved the measure.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_495">The couple had no children.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_496">In one episode, Carmen runs afoul of Daisy, the resident cow.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_497">How could I begin all over? I tasted it.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_498">He hears voices that say "Macbeth shall sleep no more.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_499">With good pace started the match with both teams alternating supremacy.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_500">Both forces are proportional to the mass of the object.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_501">He died on the voyage back.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_502">to twelve thirty a.m.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_503">Although the cast changed over the years, the main contributors were Sterling Yates, Karl Hardman, Bob Trow and Charlie Sords.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_504">The chainsaw was used to cut lake ice and trees.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_505">It is dedicated to Empress Jing.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_506">When they mature, they spin into cocoons.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_507">Adults are dark grey with black dots on the forewings.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_508">The team was led by first year head coach Darryl Rogers.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_509">This led to many people from Duchroth choosing emigration as the solution to their woes.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_510">He was court-martialed in a show-trial.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_511">This story falls under the genre of magical realism.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_512">Bush's inaction in fighting AIDS.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_513">She is not smart enough.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_514">The SJC returned a unanimous ruling on May twelfth, nineteen twenty six, upholding Judge Thayer's decisions.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_515">Monday through Saturday, and from five a.m.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_516">At some unspecified time later, he recalls that he quit his job or was fired, depending on some versions.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_517">On first April she took part in the invasion of Okinawa.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_518">He's usually happy, even when being insulted by BoJack.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_519">The Duchy was secured in the outcome of the Gothic War.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_520">It is found throughout Northern Europe.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_521">Hot weather has also encouraged use.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_522">He said it was tough but we were able to make it for five thousand yen.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_523">So, I had to debug the debugger.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_524">The remaining English had to fight a rearguard action for several miles until they reached the town.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_525">Civil law is a branch of the law.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_526">On a flat turntable, the inertia of a co-rotating object forces it off the edge.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_527">Together, they have a son, whom both of them train.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_528">His associates usually called him "T" or "the good-looking guy."</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_529">Its habitat is in grass, often on lime-rich soil (in England typically on chalk).</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_530">He now plays for Australian club Perth Glory.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_531">Both books feature the original drawing of E. H. Shepard.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_532">To clear his mind, "I drove up into the mountains with my own car."</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_533">So I was always thinking in three</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_534">The final rounds were switched to a pool-play format.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_535">It was left to his son and successor.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_536">Her mother was the youngest daughter of Queen Eleanor and Gaston the fourth.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_537">Patrick's Church River View Park</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_538">In addition, objects travelling upwards</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_539">Later, a standard-gauge network was built.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_540">Below they wore knee-length trousers.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_541">The company was toying with the idea of a news channel for a long time.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_542">The Pangu seven Star Hotel is considered to be the top luxury hotel in Beijing.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_543">Became co-regent with his father for a short time, but died at a young age.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_544">This was also recognized by the Lombards.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_545">He grew up listening to Bob Prince on KDKA Radio.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_546">running every thirty minutes throughout service times.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_547">Orthosis stretches posterior ankle structures.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_548">I think I can develop in that way but he is much stronger.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_549">His papers have digitized and catalogued.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_550">William Donohue of the Catholic League claimed the work was "hate speech", against Catholics.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_551">Some of the new art he saw.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_552">Porteous was imprisoned in the Tolbooth prison, near saint Giles church.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_553">Critics predicted that the breed would develop back, hip and leg problems similar to those that plague some Dachshunds.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_554">Sophie and Sean join a Church choir so that they can see each other more often.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_555">The title track is a French language re-working of "Woman" from previous studio album, Just Me.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_556">During try-outs, Vincent Beck as Zampano, the strongman, was replaced.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_557">The presiding judge was Webster Thayer, who was already assigned to the court before this case was scheduled.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_558">With help of a French curve one draws a curve, which has smooth contact to the osculating circles.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_559">Employee scheduling software, used for creating and distributing employee schedules, as well as for tracking employee hours.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_560">The off-screen announcer for each program was Dick Tufeld.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_561">Because the TV station was an NBC affiliate, WSLS-AM-FM switched to NBC Radio.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_562">Making Mirrors is the third studio album by Belgian-Australian artist Gotye.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_563">The soybean's outer covering is then removed and the beans are partially cooked.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_564">Brooke Vincent took over the role on twelfth May two thousand and four</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_565">The ailerons were controlled with a push-pull tube.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_566">It is caught with drag nets and dip nets but is reported to escape from nets by leaping over them.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_567">It is endemic to Afghanistan.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_568">The ants will eventually die of exhaustion.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_569">Fragments on each face are marked with letters (a, b, c).</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_570">Much of his current work deals with ethical issues in development.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_571">On his deathbed he questions them to decide which should inherit his mill.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_572">Both were issued in nineteen thirteen</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_573">The Zimbabwe Unity Movement, was a short lived political movement in Zimbabwe.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_574">He himself correctly pointed out the foul and did not measure the goals of AEL.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_575">The log phase is marked by rapid exponential growth.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_576">Without the filter an honest enjoyment.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_577">As a result, when the college re-opened, it was as an all-male college.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_578">So with more reluctance, Homer kills off the other actors until he's the only one left.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_579">He is also credited with pioneering yield management.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_580">The railway line was removed without ever being used.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_581">He was replaced with former France national team coach Jacques Santini.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_582">She loves not being like everyone else and has a unique view on the world.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_583">He was also made a life member of Scunthorpe United.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_584">Its editorial, "We Submit", earned its author a Pulitzer Prize.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_585">It was the last shot.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_586">A small number of other unusual shapes have been described, such as star-shaped bacteria.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_587">He and his brother Tom wandered down from their (and the lawyer's) First Hill neighborhood.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_588">It is found in Brazil.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_589">He lost via TKO in the first round.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_590">The characters in the game are both designed and modeled by Maya.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_591">They were formed by volcanic eruptions which had been thawed through the ice-sheet by underlying volcanic heat.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_592">For many people, it's something they have to try over and over again.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_593">The outer lip is thin, showing the external sculpture within.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_594">He is capable of a breath-hold dive to the depth of sixty feet</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_595">It was the side of the family I identified more with.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_596">He crash landed and tried to evade German infantrymen searching for him by hiding in a dyke but was captured.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_597">The materials were shipped over from the city of Amoy (now Xiamen) across the Taiwan Strait.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_598">Also in some versions, the order of the stories is reversed.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_599">The hindwings are ash grey.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_600">Android is Web-enabled from version two point three - Gingerbread.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_601">Satou had frequently worked together with Yokoyama on previous projects.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_602">However, there was some disagreement over the ending theme, which Omori and Yoshimori discussed at length over email.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_603">The lower part of men's dresses were much shorter in length than those for women.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_604">The first season premiered on twelfth June two thousand and fifteen</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_605">Kazuya and Narumi has also provided the scenario for Time Leap Paradise.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_606">Both these players were wild-card selections.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_607">At sixty seventh minute a huge chance for zero to two</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_608">Along with Praia Branca a club once existed, it never won any titles.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_609">Each vessel featured a two hundred and forty steam engine.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_610">The district is based in Perth's northern suburbs.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_611">A doctor inspects her wound and determines that the worm has nested inside the calf wound.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_612">We chose a different path.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_613">Lose Control was a commercial success peaking at number one on the Gaon Album Chart.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_614">She failed to make the top three at the Kenyan junior track trials that June.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_615">You ought to be a just people.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_616">She now works for Liz Claiborne.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_617">Notable titles included Golden Axe: The Revenge of Death Adder, Rad Mobile, OutRunners, and SegaSonic the Hedgehog.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_618">Initially announced models include RingEdge and RingWide.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_619">One day though, he is spoken to by Wyrm, who communicates to him through dreams.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_620">In nineteen sixty four he went back to Omsk and entered the actors' school of Omsk.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_621">The town's open-air stage lies immediately to the north, beneath the castle ruins.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_622">All HPEs donned flared front wings.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_623">Roch, during a part of its historic voyage through the Northwest Passage.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_624">this presumption is not fulfilled one has to know at least two conjugate diameters.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_625">It may be solitary, or form small to large groups.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_626">Dundee won the match three two</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_627">Today the lofty keep is the emblem of this small spa town.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_628">The parchment is fine and thin.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_629">Dhalia only returned to the screen in nineteen fifty two, completing three films that year.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_630">The mediaeval village court was always anxious to keep the fence around the village gapless.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_631">It is situated a few kilometers south of Shillong town.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_632">Over one million copies of the digital album has been sold on Xiami.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_633">AMT manufactured a model kit of the ZZR dragster.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_634">Others replaced on the same day included the CEO of FinBank who was replaced by Suzanne Iroche.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_635">The mouth is wide and curved, with faint furrows at the corners.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_636">Beyond the Floating Islands</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_637">The shikhara or the spire is adorned with sculptural finery.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_638">It is now a World Heritage Site.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_639">There is very little to distinguish the car from the earlier 'Turbo I.E.'</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_640">It is commonplace in traditional Scottish breakfasts.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_641">They then join a South Essex recruiting party under assumed names.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_642">He was named wall street journal's senior economics reporter in June two thousand</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_643">When The Searchlight editor T.J.S.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_644">On the Cash Box chart, the song rose as high as twenty two</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_645">The airline was headquartered at New Delhi's Airport.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_646">Whisky with Vodka, directed by Andreas Dresen Germany</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_647">They were returned after eighteen months, but the thief, although arrested, was never charged.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_648">Originally a Cherokee settlement.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_649">Although that occurred, people who believed it to be a tragedy were in the minority.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_650">He obtained the rank of lieutenant of engineers in eighteen ninety two</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_651">Strangely, that doesn't diminish Shivaraman's public relation skills.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_652">CJFB Performance Award</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_653">I also find humor in the transformations (tablecloth into mantle, skirt into halo) and hope the viewer does too.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_654">Sacco was represented by Fred H. Moore and William J. Callahan.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_655">She is unmarried with no children.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_656">Before Oz Fox joined the band, a number of guitarists almost joined Roxx Regime, including Doug Aldrich and C.C.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_657">Although his roots are in  Kerala, he lives in Bangalore with his wife Ammu.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_658">The reigning champion is Mark Allen.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_659">The beginning of the iteration was the beginning of the iteration.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_660">Before politics Chapple was a lawyer.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_661">He could also acknowledge that his own perspective had changed over time.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_662">The E twenty eight was replaced by the E thirty four in nineteen eighty eight</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_663">Each week a guest is interviewed.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_664">The Delta HF four WD was therefore pressed into service for the nineteen eighty seven season.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_665">The single charted at thirty eight</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_666">It is associated with PCOS.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_667">Every year over two hundred and fifty Irish couples choose the college chapel as a means to marry in Rome.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_668">And within the next two or three months, he moved to Long Island, to my crib.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_669">He resumed the practice of law afterwards.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_670">N A equals Round not applicable for the event</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_671">The marriage probably took place.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_672">It is released as Shaolin Executioners outside of Hong Kong and as Executioners of Death in North America.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_673">Obesity interferes with the HPA axis and stops follicular maturation.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_674">Biopsy is required to rule these out.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_675">Sound Effects Editor: Joe Reitano</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_676">Kayakers have been flying ("heli-boating") up the Perth for a number of years.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_677">The cardinal's will directed that the college should be placed under the charge of the Jesuits.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_678">The college now passed from the care of the Jesuits, and an Italian priest was made rector.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_679">A permanent lead singer was found during that tour, the band's drum technician; Trey Oswald.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_680">Both had done work with Stephen Stills.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_681">"Shout" with the appearance that deserves to be in the lineup</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_682">The Beaver is often exploited by others or becomes the victim of malicious persons.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_683">Along the way he encounters the comely Ying Chun, herself a master of the Crane style.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_684">The play was quite a challenge for her.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_685">The law was repealed after the end of the war.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_686">Her eyelids then open to reveal lifeless eyes, from which begin to emerge the antennas.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_687">They used the Roman salute and also used to shout the name of Salazar in their parades.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_688">And I like how these cooties are funny in a way.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_689">Masaaki Suzuki began playing organ professionally at church services at the age of twelve</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_690">After having spent three seasons with Forest, Mills joined Barnsley.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_691">It was fun, romantic, solid.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_692">The firm is still in business.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_693">Epic Facework: Self-presentation and Social Interaction in Homer.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_694">Sophie returns to the street with Rosie.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_695">The Ringedge also supports three D game capability.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_696">Man, woman and child in the community.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_697">The stem is encased in a sheath.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_698">Other phone system vendors are now also offering these features for internal voicemail users.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_699">With three strikers started the game of the lift.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_700">But in the second half neither team risked and stayed one to one until the end on March thirty first</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_701">A photo of her is shown below in the gallery.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_702">I'd have paid good money to stay out of this place.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_703">Saint Paul's Heritage Church - former Anglican Church</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_704">The base is cushioned, with cable moulding.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_705">The operating principle involves inducing a vibration of the tube through which the fluid passes.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_706">Cyril Tommasone (born fourth July nineteen eighty seven) is a French artistic gymnast.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_707">It's located in the Binjiang District, Hangzhou City, Zhejiang Province, People's Republic of China.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_708">Junior Hockey League teams - Defunct</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_709">The band members knew each other from the college they were all attending, Virginia Commonwealth University, in Richmond, Virginia.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_710">The band plays with laser precision and songs move smoothly through riffs and transitions.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_711">The second wing of his "Lay oh two Sheep Signing Promo" continued at Shenzhen on October twenty ninth</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_712">The rebrand saw viewers engaging with the channel.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_713">Kittens bearing two copies of the munchkin gene will not develop in the womb.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_714">The device is able to draw any ellipse with a fixed sum</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_715">The normal rafting put in at Five-Finger stream gives a nice class III-IV run with one amazing gorge.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_716">New York: Cambridge University Press.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_717">"Thou has not well learnt thy trade" The second son says he will take half, and gets the same reply.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_718">He was the founder of a Zaidi kingdom that endured, under many vicissitudes, until nineteen sixty two</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_719">on the French national television for two years.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_720">The Beaver was relegated to the background.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_721">Stutzman responded with a letter from her lawyer.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_722">His rock opera was eventually sabotaged by BoJack, who took advantage of his former addiction to video games.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_723">The twenty defendants were discharged by Special Judge V. B. Gupta.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_724">Most of the railway has now gone, but Lelydorp survives and is now the capital of Wanica District.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_725">It was, I thought, the most delicious medley of sweet flavors I had ever tasted.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_726">The method uses standards of proof.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_727">The caudal fin is asymmetrical with the lower lobe being longer than the upper lobe.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_728">He qualified as a teacher then graduated as a lawyer from the National University of the Littoral.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_729">He performed "Lose Control" for the first time on The Show on November fifteenth</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_730">It is locally pronounced "Marlows".</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_731">The points with vertical tangents, vertices</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_732">Ori (born September second, nineteen seventy) is a Vancouver, BC lawyer and filmmaker.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_733">He opened a practice, Lee and Boal, with Charles Herbert Lee in eighteen ninety one at Denver.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_734">This line is due to be upgraded to broad gauge.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_735">After the conclusion of the war, Ulrikh presided over a number of the early trials.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_736">The goal came early in the replay at the fifty second minute after a superb effort past Gonzalez and Kozatsik.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_737">Sato fifty seven' leader Nikolaos long shot sent the ball out.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_738">They rescue Nonahkee, but Kuechler and his main army escape, leaving the Confederacy to dissolve.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_739">He received the Booth Gardner Mental Health Champion award from Sound Mental Health in two thousand and eleven</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_740">one thousand two hundred and nine, is the history in miniature of Romish jealousy and exclusiveness.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_741">Each year's winner was determined by the previous year's sales.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_742">Individually she did not reach the semi-finals.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_743">in eighteen sixty five using Chinese architects.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_744">Leonards-on-Sea, Sussex and typed out his first story at the age of eight.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_745">Bengal Film Journalists' Association Awards</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_746">Considine tried selling out to Marcus Loew</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_747">Lesbian couples can get access to IVF as well.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_748">The song, however, failed to reach the top one hundred</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_749">The most common mothertongue among the population was English.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_750">It covered the straps attaching the upper legs to the breastplate.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_751">A boy who testified admitted to rehearsing his testimony.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_752">Some have suggested they did so because of cowardice.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_753">It was an improved version  from which was possible to make an upgrade.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_754">With help of one, one easily checks that</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_755">The special case of a moving circle with radius</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_756">The average household size was two point three seven</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_757">They were replaced by Victor Dominicis (Vic Venom) and Rick Griffith (Rick Royale) respectively.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_758">He moved right in to my apartment.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_759">Cordic died in Los Angeles of brain cancer in nineteen ninety nine, one month short of his seventy third birthday.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_760">According to Shahid, it is clear that David's killers were from allied tribes seeking to weaken the dominant Salihids.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_761">He may have been delegated this authority by King David.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_762">No artwork was created for this second single.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_763">After her mother dies, her sister Jane (Virginia Madsen) and Jane's boyfriend Lou (Tom Irwin) eject her.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_764">Masuoka takes her home and tries to civilize her, referring to her as a modern-day analog of Kaspar Hauser.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_765">Another key component of this junction is the protein myosin and primarily its interaction with vezatin.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_766">The winners of each group joined Angola (holders) into the final round.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_767">Jasem Al-Tamimi was the party's secretary general.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_768">The new bridge was safely completed with no major problems.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_769">The nucleoid contains the chromosome with its associated proteins and RNA.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_770">In cell division, two identical clone daughter cells are produced.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_771">Professor Basil Charles King (nineteen fifteen to nineteen eighty five) was a British Geologist and author.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_772">In eighteen sixty two, secretary of Alford, mister Cure, continued Alford's work.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_773">They allow the application of Newton's laws to a rotating system.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_774">At the upper part of the cathedral, there is 'The Wounded Angel.'</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_775">His remarks received a standing ovation from the audience.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_776">John Veryard held the seat for a single term, losing it to Gill in nineteen oh eight</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_777">It is left to Hung Hsi-Kuan to lead the remaining students to safety.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_778">He went on to write four more books and a memoir.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_779">Originally from Bloomfield, NJ, he is a graduate of Trenton State College (now The College of New Jersey).</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_780">Fellows are traditionally introduced at the ISCB's flagship Intelligent Systems for Molecular Biology conference each year.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_781">Lamb of God has toured with the Ozzfest twice.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_782">Since nineteen twenty one she used her pseudonym Maria.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_783">She left her library job but continued copy editing.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_784">The upper part of dresses could now be tailored exactly to the body.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_785">They often are worn with chunky black boots," writes AP reporter Anne Kim.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_786">The Traditionals or Independents did not affiliate with either tribe.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_787">Gerard had over thirty children, including Benjamin Vandergucht, a painter and art dealer.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_788">During the post-war period, hunger and unemployment increased.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_789">Wettstein charges it with being altered from the Latin.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_790">Holders of NuShares earn rewards as an incentive to stabilize the network.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_791">The dependency can be described by an index ellipsoid.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_792">In nineteen ninety, Bakija (playing both guitar and bass), Madriaga, and Rubinstein recorded a final album, Volume two</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_793">It is the northernmost strongpoint in the Siegfried Line.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_794">A little egret is standing at the tail of the dragon.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_795">Business users then review their work flow and revise it if necessary.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_796">Rosie tells Sophie who the troll is and they both go to confront Gina.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_797">The club then moved to the Spartan League, and finished top of the league.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_798">Centro in the USA is now independently known as Brixmor.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_799">Neither are not known any interaction between them in following years.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_800">It is known from Australia, and was introduced to the Solomon Islands, Indonesia, Singapore and Vietnam.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_801">The Huron replaced the Iroquois, the Cheyenne replaced the Lakota (Sioux) and the Zapotec replaced the Aztec.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_802">An idol of this size and beauty is rarely to be found.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_803">In another episode, he becomes attached to a lost Chihuahua until his owner comes to claim him.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_804">He and his wife Colleen live in Seattle's Maple Leaf neighborhood with their twins.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_805">This closed a case of bank fraud in which Chatwal had been embroiled for over a decade.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_806">Four charges were filed by the CBI, with Chatwal named a defendant in two.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_807">In an arch in the wall of the south aisle, there is an effigy of Sir John Sewell, knight.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_808">It also strongly suggests that it may have been copied in Egypt.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_809">Evan Longoria, Alex Cobb, and Ben Zobrist endorsed Martinez.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_810">After his final release from prison Fiumara lived on Long Island.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_811">Mary Susan Hoffman Lead Graphic Designer of The Hammonton Gazette.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_812">In seventeen seventy seven, Unanue moved to Lima to study natural sciences.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_813">Historic documents state that three towers with churches, among them saint George.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_814">Dudley was one of the first students to enroll.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_815">He spent the next fifteen years teaching in Wilmington.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_816">The overhaul was Dudley's approach to addressing all of the problems.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_817">It was her first mainstream Bangladeshi film in collaboration with Shakib Khan.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_818">Masked gunmen immediately opened fire on the occupants with automatic weapons.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_819">August two thousand and seven, Regis and Joy Philbin announced that their daughter J.J.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_820">Kamay Lau is a British actress, best known as the failed hitlady in Revolver.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_821">He scrapes them out of the doll's face and buys himself a pocket watch.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_822">Between the labia majora and the inner thighs are the labiocrural folds.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_823">The car is available also with semi-automatic parking assistant.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_824">Lava City is a member of the Women's Flat Track Derby Association (WFTDA).</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_825">He is a member of the South Korean-Chinese boy group Exo and its sub-unit Exo-M.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_826">Old projects could now be imported from the file with some limitations.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_827">The National League champion benefited from this rule for the first time in two thousand and ten</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_828">The Marion County Courthouse was built during eighteen eighty four to eighteen eighty six</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_829">Its anchor tenants are Marshalls, Safeway, and Walmart.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_830">Can be obtained from the derivative of the standard representation</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_831">The house is now owned by the wife of an American diplomat, missis Joan Dale.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_832">William had participated in the Norman conquest of England.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_833">He is smaller than most animals, being only slightly taller than Roo.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_834">However, the area was subject to clear cutting for row agriculture by early settlers.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_835">In eighteen sixteen he relocated to Zurich in order to conduct historical research.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_836">Sean Tully (Antony Cotton) tells Sophie he saw her twin at the Manchester Gay Pride event.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_837">She tries to open up to Sally but is overlooked in favour of Jeff, her new boyfriend.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_838">Sprite capabilities: Multiple buffering, four framebuffers</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_839">There comes a time of spring, when everyone in the land is filled with joy.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_840">He also saw action the following year in the Huon Peninsula during the New Guinea campaign.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_841">July two thousand seven: Totte's works were displayed in Helsinki.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_842">In nineteen fifty two, a TV station was added, Channel ten WSLS-TV.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_843">In nineteen ninety six, his ashes were scattered on the White House lawn.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_844">Bridgestone, Dunlop and Yokohama had supplied tyres until nineteen eighty seven</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_845">The old offices of the stadium will be joint area outside the locker room, journalistic theory, clinics and other.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_846">Then the long striding James began to flail in quicksand.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_847">Of Ivorian descent, Diaby also possesses "superb touch" and "excellent close control".</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_848">Three days later, Diaby scored the third goal in a five to two Champions League group stage win.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_849">Prior to Diaby's expulsion, Arsenal had been leading the match four to zero</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_850">He makes more of a physical impact in a game, in midfield.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_851">She enjoyed great popularity, but her pregnancies ruined her health.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_852">Amit Gupta is the current CEO of Asianet News Media and Entertainment private limited</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_853">However, liquid growth media are used when measurement of growth or large volumes of cells are required.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_854">One species of Rickettsia causes typhus, while another causes Rocky Mountain spotted fever.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_855">In another episode, the Beaver kindly lets a strange boy ride his bike only to have the boy steal it.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_856">The show ends with the Beaver and Wally playing with a wind-up toy and laughing like children.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_857">In two thousand and ten, he made his directorial debut with the film Huge.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_858">Benjamin Franklin Keller was a United States federal judge.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_859">It is a leading example of the Alexandrian text-type.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_860">He failed to finish the longer race and came sixteenth in the five thousand meter final.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_861">Another visualization of the Coriolis and centrifugal forces is this animation clip.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_862">The ball's path through the air is straight when viewed by observers standing on the ground (right panel).</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_863">The time taken for the mass to complete a full circle</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_864">The next day I received a present from the Prince, a jeweled ring, a panama hat and a cane.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_865">He was popularly known among his devotees as His Holiness</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_866">He was due to meet with union officials across the road but the large crowd initially prevented him.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_867">Union members thus cleared a path through the crowd for Menzies to walk to the meeting with officials.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_868">Then the device appears to go out of control and speed up (sometimes with pyrotechnics for added drama).</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_869">One peculiarity is the clock mechanism, which has to be wound up by hand every day.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_870">Serving Norheim and Staudernheim are railway stations on the Valley Railway.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_871">Gooch and Smith refused to answer the bill and to appear, saying it was void.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_872">The Edmonton Opera is also the largest employer of the Edmonton Symphony Orchestra.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_873">The maximum width of this type of moth is one hundred millimeters</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_874">He allegedly shot dead a childhood friend over a simple dispute.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_875">He was born in Offenburg and raised by Jesuits until the order was dissolved in seventeen seventy three</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_876">It is the speed at which an electrochemical impulse propagates down a neural pathway.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_877">John Lodge, who plays John Stamp, never reveals his face onscreen.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_878">Also, these business applications are built to use certain kind of Business transactions or data items.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_879">The album featured two of his Billboard's hit singles: "Whateva Man" and "It's Like That (My Big Brother)".</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_880">Meanwhile, Alice runs into a storm and finds herself shipwrecked on the island where the Village is located.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_881">It may be viewed as a distinct genre field, rather than music that overlaps with pop and rock.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_882">Hollywood figures, such as actress Bette Davis, have graced the hotel.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_883">When Hotaru is a teenager, she shares some pudding with Gin before she leaves at the end of the summer.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_884">ISMB conference proceedings have been published in Bioinformatics since two thousand and one</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_885">The attack was to destroy the German troops around Kirovograd and capture the city from the north and south.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_886">He leads a reign of terror until defeated by his former ally Macduff.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_887">Macbeth becomes a tyrant, brutally stamping out any real or perceived threats to his power.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_888">In nineteen eighty three he returned to Japan, where he began teaching at Kobe Shoin Women's University.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_889">In nineteen eighty five the French fashion designer Jean-Paul Gaultier created his first skirt for a men.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_890">After weeks of secret deliberation that included interviews with the judge, lawyers, and several witnesses, the commission upheld the verdict.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_891">Milltown is an unincorporated community in western Butler County, Missouri.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_892">To Ukrainian government, Constitution of Ukraine is nothing but toilet paper.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_893">McKay produced Irvine Welsh's first short film Nuts and also wrote and directed a short film called Recipe.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_894">They come across a run-down music school and take shelter with its owner, the Maestro.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_895">Mignon, the Princess and Samson remain with the Maestro at his music school.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_896">NuBits is a cryptocurrency which advertises itself as a stablecoin issued by a DAO under the same name.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_897">Tangent slope as parameter: A parametric representation, which uses the slope.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_898">The effect is even more evident under a vaulted roof shaped as a section of a prolate spheroid.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_899">If the display is an ellipse, rather than a straight line, the two signals are out of phase.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_900">These algorithms need only a few multiplications and additions to calculate each vector.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_901">It features a number of rapids and passes through two gorges before meeting the Whataroa River.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_902">Less than one percent of the transmitted power is used for conveying the modulated data.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_903">This beer was supposedly brewed by Sir Reginald Frothingslosh at Upper Crudney-on-the-Thames.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_904">However, the statement about Dawud's newfound piety "is correct and cannot be viewed with suspicion".</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_905">The museum is only open to casual visitors on Sundays and public holidays (during the summer).</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_906">The animals suffer massive casualties, but in the end manage to drive the basilisks to death.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_907">If the volcano breaches the surface of the glacier it will be topped by a subaerially erupted lava plateau.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_908">A select few fifth are also awarded a Prefect badge.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_909">Theo and Luke try to establish their innocence, but Nell tells them that they don't know her.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_910">Russian-speaking nobility of Polish-Ukrainian descent could be an aim to different forces.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_911">Despite being sunny, summers have a lot of rain, with thunderstorms being quite common.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_912">Bliss, Texas, and later for the Space Flight Center in Huntsville, Alabama.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_913">However several species of bacteria are pathogenic and cause infectious diseases, including cholera, syphilis, anthrax, leprosy, and bubonic plague.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_914">The marches and boycotts against the Dera continued, until the situation subsided after several weeks.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_915">Excessive licking of the forelegs (another abnormal behaviour) is common in stall and tether systems.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_916">It was first hoisted at midnight on February eighteenth, nineteen sixty five, the day the Gambia became an independent country.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_917">When the late nineteen eighties and early nineteen nineties approached, fewer alternates were worn for the games.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_918">The ideology of Arab parties varies, although most are secular in their political outlook.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_919">The couple had several children, whose names are unknown.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_920">He was a member of Russian nationalist organization Union of the Russian People in Kyiv.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_921">In December two thousand and three, the Rocky Mountain Regional Bioinformatics conference, Rocky one, was launched in Aspen, Colorado.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_922">The manuscript was also examined by John Wordsworth.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_923">Born in Hazelridge, Manitoba, he joined the Royal Canadian Mounted Police in nineteen forty two</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_924">The driver was Joel Rifkin, later convicted as a serial killer responsible for the murder of several prostitutes.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_925">In the summer of that year she took part in Operation Crossroads, the atomic weapons tests at Bikini.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_926">This film won National Awards in ten categories, including the Best Actress Award for Ahsan.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_927">Both videos recorded in Sweden in January two thousand and seven, and additional photage for "Numb" during the fall.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_928">Kittens bearing one munchkin gene and one normal gene will be short-legged munchkins.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_929">The Iranian army took advantage of its conflicts with the Communist Party, Toudeh, to commit massacres.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_930">He now works for the Japan Football Association to help younger referees to develop their skills.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_931">Jack of All Trades is a two thousand and seven album by Stones Throw rapper Wildchild.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_932">It was also used for Super Hang-On (nineteen eighty seven) and Turbo Outrun (nineteen eighty nine)</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_933">while still maintaining links with the student chapter of SPJ at Stony Brook.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_934">The square in front of the building is known as Opera Square.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_935">The trial judge vacated the verdict and found for the defendants, but the Ninth Circuit reinstated the verdict.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_936">The Saturday Night Live spin-off series, first introduced in Big Brother three, saw Housemates competing in live tasks.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_937">In order to prevent piracy, as well as illegal bootleg games, many System sixteen boards used an encryption system.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_938">Gauss used the summit of Falkenberg, amongst others, as a triangulation station for his land surveys.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_939">The figure shows a bird's-eye view based upon the same ball speed on forward and return paths.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_940">The station motto was 'Transmitting from the center of the island'</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_941">The ministry has been based in Springfield, Massachusetts since two thousand and eight</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_942">Damages on peroneal nerves destroy the myelin sheath that covers the axon or the whole nerve cell.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_943">The facility of this airmail service was also extended to a private courier.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_944">During his professional boxing career he was trained by Bob Shannon a long-time Manchester boxing coach.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_945">It publishes the world's oldest women's magazine, Women and Society, established in eighteen eighty five</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_946">She married Alexander Balas, Demetrius the second Nicator and Antiochus VII Sidetes.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_947">Logical Dialogue-Games and Fallacies, Lanham, Maryland, University Press of America, nineteen eighty four</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_948">Newton's laws of motion describe the motion of an object in an inertial (non-accelerating) frame of reference.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_949">Dialog Theory for Critical Argumentation, Amsterdam, John Benjamins Publishers, two thousand and seven</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_950">Super Duper Super Sleuths two thousand and ten DVD</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_951">It was introduced in a two thousand and ten paper by Dana Carney, Amy Cuddy, and Andy Yap.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_952">Finch's modeling career kick-started in two thousand and four when she won the Queensland Model of the Year title.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_953">One fish may eat many of these organisms, causing the DDT and PCBs to accumulate in fish tissue.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_954">On recognising the beauty of Mignon's singing voice Fevvers introduces her to the Princess of Abyssinia.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_955">Monstercat five Year Anniversary features several recurring artists from previous Monstercat compilation albums including Stonebank, Tristam, and Noisestorm.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_956">However, after the season, South China decided to voluntarily self-relegate in order to cut costs.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_957">She also worked in theatre where she featured in two different plays Poore Chand Ki Raat and Ichha.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_958">The film was photographed by Abe Levy, after hours, in a Fed-Ex Kinkos without corporate knowledge.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_959">It uses the GPU-accelerated ray tracing engine developed by the NVIDIA Advanced Rendering Center to provide interactive product visualisations.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_960">He studied law, was admitted to the bar in eighteen thirty, and commenced practice in Centreville.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_961">He lost the Republican primary election to Mike Braun, coming in second with thirty percent of the vote.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_962">to make methane (natural gas) via water electrolysis and the subsequent application of the Sabatier reaction.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_963">Capcom's CPS one and CPS two boards were built on a similar foundation, as was SNK's Neo Geo hardware.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_964">He served as the President of TAIK from nineteen eighty six until two thousand and eight</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_965">These distinctions are awarded in honour of outstanding contributions to the fields of computational biology and bioinformatics.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_966">She compiled "the most comprehensive Native American string figure collection ever assembled from a single tribe [or nation]"</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_967">The first Lightworks product was demonstrated at the nineteen ninety Autofact exhibition in Detroit, USA.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_968">However, Naomi has twice as much system memory, twice as much video memory, and four times as much sound memory.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_969">Sophie soon became suspicious of Kevin's new girlfriend, Jenny Bradley's (Sally Ann Matthews) growing attachment to her brother Jack.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_970">The lyrics are substituted and recorded to the tune of the Judas Priest song, "Heading Out to the Highway".</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_971">Upon arriving at the specified address, looking for a rabbit named Aki-chan, he finds that there is no rabbit.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_972">It has a population of seven thousand four hundred and fifty four and is located seventeen kilometers south.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_973">Digital dashboards, also known as business intelligence dashboards, enterprise dashboards, or executive dashboards.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_974">It is available for sale (seventy five cents a copy) at more than seventy locations in Hammonton, Folsom, Waterford</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_975">Along with He Jingzhi, he is considered as one of the major practitioners of "political lyric poetry" style.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_976">On tenth April, Diaby scored his second goal of the season in a three to one win against Blackpool.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_977">reasons versus causal history of reason explanations, do the differences emerge.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_978">But he used to say religion did not need to have a long face, and he made religion upbeat.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_979">Virginian Horton Barker was recorded singing "The Millers Will" in nineteen sixty two,</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_980">Wonuarra is a locality southeast of Paringa in the east end of the South Australian Riverland region.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_981">In December Germans retreated as the World War two finished</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_982">It helped organize a community bathhouse, a community swimming pool, and the Sanders County Historical Library.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_983">Totte worked on a new series of oil paintings called "Dismantled Sculptures".</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_984">Vaughn moved into television in nineteen seventy nine at CBS-affiliate WNAC, now WHDH-TV.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_985">On tenth July, Park formally announced her two thousand and twelve presidential bid at the Time Square, Yeongdeungpo District, Seoul.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_986">Because Oil States' appeal challenged the America Invents Acts, the federal government joined as a respondent to the case.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_987">He studied at Oxford and was appointed vicar of the church of Bringhurst.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_988">In Austria, the five hundred and twenty five E was detuned to eighty eight kilowatts.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_989">He died at Ashtead, after a lingering illness, on first February seventeen eighty seven, in his sixty-first year.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_990">The band played thirty six shows in the United States and finished the tour in San Juan, Puerto Rico.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_991">In january two thousand and ten Stefan Westerberg left the band and was replaced.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_992">Chapple Lighthouse built two thousand and three Barwick Waterfront</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_993">It is a localized increase of hematopoietic bone marrow that creates a radiolucent radiographic defect.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_994">The engine was an eight two L fuel injected four cylinder with balancing shafts.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_995">Brand Nubian Lord Jamar criticized Kanye West wearing skirts, saying that his style has no place in hip-hop.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_996">Dorsey Schroeder is a race car driver born February fifth, nineteen fifty three in Kirkwood, Missouri.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_997">Arguer's Position: A Pragmatic Study of Ad Hominem Attack, Criticism, Refutation, and Fallacy, Westport, Connecticut, Greenwood Press, nineteen eighty five</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_998">Eight hundred AD, whose illustrations embellished traditional Christian iconography with ornate, swirling motifs.</fileid>
  <fileid id="z0001_999">Finch's partner is Michael, the partner to the original winner of Dancing with the Stars, Bec Cartwright.</fileid>
</recording_script>
