<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<text_sources>
  <!-- automatically generated by gen_corpus.py on 2019-04-09 at 12:23:11 -->
  <!-- Hand editted to remove references and headings -->
  <!-- Sample for testsing other scripts  -->
  <text_source id="Beckfoot School">
    <text>
      Beckfoot School is a coeducational secondary school and sixth form with academy status, located in Bingley, West Yorkshire, England.
      The school has previously gained Technology College status, specialist school status in the Arts, Artsmark Gold and a Sportsmark Award. It also has a Charter Mark for services to the community and is a City Learning Centre. The school converted to academy status in August 2013. In December 2016, the school received World Class school quality mark. It is one of the three first schools in northern England to get the status.
      Beckfoot School is also a training school that has attained 'Investors in People' and a 'School Achievement Award'. The school moved into new, purpose-built, premises in June 2011 and the old buildings were demolished in 2012.  The new premises are shared with Hazelbeck School.
      The school has above-average A*–C grades in GCSEs and is taking part in the new fast-track Modern Foreign Language and Media Studies GCSE scheme.

      The School's sixth form was awarded Grade 1 (outstanding) status in its June 2014 Ofsted inspection. Qualifications offered are A-Levels and BTEC national diploma.

      As an academy, Beckfoot School is the founding school of the Beckfoot Trust, a multi-academy trust. Hazelbeck School joined the trust in 2013 and Beckfoot Upper Heaton in 2015. Beckfoot Thornton joined in 2016. Former head teacher, David Horn, is the head of the Beckfoot Trust, and was replaced with Gillian Halls as head teacher.

      Girls Aloud star Kimberley Walsh – attended the school under its previous name of Beckfoot Grammar School
      Georgina Roberts – England Ladies Rugby Union attended Beckfoot until 2002
      Footballer Danny Ward – attended the school
      Footballer James Hanson – attended the school from 1999–2004
      Katie Pattison-Hart – member of the first female crew of five to row the Atlantic
    </text>
  </text_source>
  <text_source id="Dhool Parakuthu">
    <text>
      Dhool Parakuthu is a 1993 Tamil-language Indian feature film directed by Raja, starring Raghuvaran in lead role.
      Dhool Parakuthu is the story of Raghuvaran, a man with golden heart loved by Ramya Krishnan. Raghuvaran's family get killed by Malaysia Vasudevan and his henchmen. Now Raghuvaran wants to take law in his hand, but he is stopped by his police officer friend Ravi Raghavendra. Will Raghuvaran completes his revenge form the climax.
    </text>
  </text_source>
  <text_source id="Johannes Bapst">
    <text>
      Johannes Bapst (b. at La Roche, Fribourg, Switzerland, 17 December 1815; d. at Mount Hope, Maryland, U.S.A., 2 November 1887) was a Swiss  Jesuit missionary and educator. He became the first President of Boston College.

      At 12 he began his studies at the college of Fribourg, and on 30 September 1835, entered the novitiate of the Society of Jesus. He was ordained priest, 31 December 1846, after the usual course of studies and teaching.
      He arrived in New York in 1848 and, ignorant of English, was sent to minister to the Native Americans at Old Town, Maine. They had been without a priest for twenty years. He founded several temperance societies in Maine.
      In 1850 he left Old Town for Eastport. His work immediately began to attract attention, both for its results among Catholics and the number of converts who were brought into the Church. As his missions covered a large extent of territory, he became generally known through the state. When the Know-Nothing excitement broke out he was at Ellsworth. Protestants were outraged when he denounced the public schools for forcing a Protestant Bible on Catholic children. He moved to Bangor. The Ellsworth town meeting passed a resolution threatening him bodily if he returned. He did return on a brief visit in October 1854 and was attacked by ruffians, robbed of his watch and money, tarred and feathered, and ridden out of town on a rail. The incident was met with general condemnation across Maine and New England.In Bangor, Maine, Father Bapst built the first Catholic church, dedicated in 1856. He remained there for three years and was then sent to Boston College, as rector of what was at that time the house of higher studies for the Jesuit scholastics. He was afterwards superior of all the Jesuit houses of Canada and New York, and subsequently superior of a Residence in Providence, Rhode Island.
    </text>
  </text_source>
  <text_source id="PinchukArtCentre">
    <text>
      PinchukArtCentre is a centre of contemporary art, located in Kyiv with a collection of works by Ukranian and international artists. The museum was opened on 16 September 2006 by the steel billionaire Victor Pinchuk.The mission of the PinchukArtCentre mission is to exhibit new artistic production and collecting national and international contemporary art. It is a venue for seminal working artists who represent the complexity of our time, addressing important issues and complexities.The centre's objectives consist of an international collection, exhibitions, education programmes, publications and research.
      The PinchukArtCentre is the largest private museum in Eastern Europe. In 2007 and 2009, the PinchukArtCentre officially represented Ukraine at the Venice Biennale. Admission to the museum is free.

      To the date, the PinchukArtCentre has presented major exhibitions:

      “New Space”, an opening exhibition by the various international and Ukrainian artists;
      “Generations.UsA”, a group show with twenty young Ukrainian and American artists;
      “Vik Muniz: A Survey”, an exhibition by the well-known Brazilian artist Vik Muniz;
      “An Instinctive Eye”, a selection of contemporary photography from the Sir Elton John Collection;
      “REFLECTION”, a recent acquisitions exhibition including artists such as: Serhiy Bratkov, Antony Gormley, Andreas Gursky, Damien Hirst, Jeff Koons and Takashi Murakami;
      “Mariko Mori: Oneness”, a large scale exhibition by the Japanese artist, Mariko Mori;
      “Paul McCartney — Paintings”, a survey exhibition of paintings by Sir Paul McCartney;
      “Rhine on The Dnipro: Julia Stoschek Collection / Andreas Gursky”, a thematic video art exhibition with seventeen international artists and major one-person photography exhibition;
      Exhibition of the British artist Sam Taylor-Wood and “21 RUSSIA”, a group showcase of contemporary Russian artists.
      “REQUIEM”, the largest retrospective show of the British artist Damien Hirst;
      Exhibition of 20 shortlisted artists for the PinchukArtCentre Prize and a group show of Ukrainian artists of the elder generation “RED FOREST”;
      Two parallel solo exhibitions: “Faith Matters” by Indian Subodh Gupta and “Ukraine” by Sergey Bratkov;
      Sexuality and Transcendence – a major international group exhibition;
      Solo exhibition of Takashi Murakami;
      21 Shortlisted Artists of the Future Generation Art Prize Group Exhibition;
      Solo exhibition of the South African artist Candice Breitz: "You+I";
      Solo show by Mexican artist Damian Ortega “Tool Bit”;
      "Collection Platform 1: Circulation";
      "Your emotional future", solo exhibition by Olafur Eliasson;
      Solo Exhibition of Cinthia Marcelle, the winner of the Main Prize of the Future Generation Art Prize 2010;
      Exhibition of the 20 shortlisted artists for the PinchukArtCentre Prize 2011;
      "If there is no water running from your tap" – a solo exhibition by Ukrainian artist Oleksandr Roytburd in the context of РАС-UA;
      "Backside entrance to the museum" by Iliya Chichkan and Psyfox, a РАС-UA project.Apart from large scale projects, the art centre holds short term PAC-UA exhibitions presenting only new works by Ukrainian artists. All PAC-UA showcases are held in the special art space on the 5th floor of the PinchukArtCentre.
      In 2008 - 2009, the Art Centre presented shows within Project Room concept — a special series of exhibitions by the young and emerging artists. Exhibitions have included: «Pastime Paradise» by Christina Solomukha (France/Ukraine); «East Art Map» by IRWIN (Slovenia); «Patriotism. Art as a Present» by R.E.S. (Ukraine); «Dreamers» by SOSka (Ukraine) and a solo exhibition by Keita Sugiura (Japan).
      In 2007 and 2009, PinchukArtCentre officially organized the Ukrainian Pavilion at the 52nd and 53rd Biennale in Venice, with projects “A Poem About an Inland Sea” and “Steppes of Dreamers” respectively. In 2011 the art centre presented exhibition Future Generation Art Prize @ Venice -Ukrainian Collateral Event on the 54th Venice Biennale.
      In late 2008, the PinchukArtCentre Prize was announced: the first national prize for young artists up to 35 years old. 20 shortlisted artists were selected among more than 1100 applications and an international jury chose the winners of the Main Prize and two Special Prizes. Artem Volokitin from Kharkiv won the Main Prize, and Masha Shubina and Oleksii Salmanov got two Special Prizes. The PinchukArtCentre Prize award ceremony was held on December 4, 2009.
      In 2011, the PinchukArtCentre Prize Expert Committee reviewed more than 1,000 applications received from young artists from all over Ukraine and abroad, and formed a shortlist of the Prize nominees. As part of a group exhibition of 20 shortlisted artists, 20 new artists’ statements, specially produced with the support of the PinchukArtCentre for the show, were presented at the art centre.
      Laureates of the PinchukArtCentre Prize 2011 were announced at the Award Ceremony that took place on December 9, 2011, in Kyiv. The winner of the Main Prize was Mykyta Kadan; Zhanna Kadyrova and Serhiy Radkevych won two Special Prizes, and the Public Choice Prize went to Mykyta Shalennyi.
      On December 8, 2009, the Victor Pinchuk Foundation announced the establishment of the Future Generation Art Prize, a new large-scale international competition for artists up to 35 years old, with the PinchukArtCentre acting as the organizer.
      On June 29, 2010, seven members of the Selection Committee featuring competent and global art-professionals, selected 20 artists from more than 6,000 applications coming from 125 countries and divided over all continents. The 21th nominee for the Future Generation Art Prize is Artem Volokitin, the winner of the first PinchukArtCentre Prize 2009.
      On February 6, 2012, application process for the second edition of the biennial Future Generation Art Prize was launched. Applications from all young artists are available online from February 6 through May 6, 2012, at the competition’s website: futuregenerationartprize.org
      On December 10, 2010, at the Future Generation Art Prize 2010 Award Ceremony the names of the winners were announced: a Brazilian artist Cinthia Marcelle received the Main Prize and Mircea Nicolae, the artist from Romania, won the Special Prize.
      In February 2011 the PinchukArtCentre presented “Collection Platform: Circulation project”, a permanent exhibition of selected works from the collection representing leading International and Ukrainian contemporary artists. The collection platform is renewed twice a year.
      In October 2011 PinchukArtCentre opened an application call for the new Curatorial Platform – a two-year full-time program combining a theoretical and practical training. The programme is open for all Ukrainians up to 30 and will give them access to develop their competence on a high international professional level to become an expert in the curatorial work, exhibition, communication, publication, education, technique in the context of contemporary art museum.
      Based on the decision of the selection committee, the first Curatorial Platform participants, chosen from more than 130 applicants, were Lizaveta German (23 years, Kyiv), Tatiana Kochubynska (26 years, Kyiv), Oleksandr Mykhed (23 years, Kyiv), Maria Lanko (25 years, Kyiv) and Kateryna Radchenko (27 years, Odesa). These selected applicants started their two-year residency program in January 2012.
      As of February 2012, the total number of PinchukArtCentre visitors since its opening reached over 1,475,000 people.
    </text>
  </text_source>
  <text_source id="Steel Panther discography">
    <text>
      The discography of American heavy metal band Steel Panther consists of four studio albums, one extended play, two video albums and fourteen singles.
    </text>
  </text_source>
</text_sources>
